topdownloads.net 2010-11-21

# Topdownloads: Free Software Downloads Download Music, Games, ScreenSavers & Computer Software

At Topdwonloads Networks, we are committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy covers the exchange of personal information on this web site. The following points will be explained more detailed below: 

  1. What personal information is collected; 
  2. How this information is used; 
  3. With whom the information will be shared. 

Any personal information you provide at this web site, like your personal links and address book, will be saved to a database. This way you can always access your personal information, regardless from the place you are. 

We use cookies to save some implicit information, like which 'content blocks' are opened, minimized or which are closed. If you selected so, your ID and password are saved in cookies as well. This way we can present your personalized startpage each time your visit. 

Information you provide when contacting us will only be used to respond adequatly to your message. E-mail addresses you may have provided for our mailing lists will only be used to send mailings. 

Topdwonloads Networks will not disclose any of your personal information to any outside organization. All information you provide at this web site will be kept confidential. 

* Make sure you've read the Terms of Use, which describes certain usage conditions. In short it says that the use of any of our services is at your own risk.
* Topdwonloads Networks uses cookies so that you can create a personalized starpage. If you want to learn more about cookies, please read our Cookie Statement.
* We are very concerned about your privacy. We don't provide any personal information to third parties. Please read our Privacy Policy for more information on this subject.
